umac.mo 2006-06-17

# University of Macau - Privacy Policy Statement

|  |   
---  
|  |  |    
---|---  

### University Privacy Policy

The University of Macau undertakes, in its data management policies and practices, to observe the spirit of the data protection principles and to comply with the requirements of the **Law of Protection of Personal Data (Privacy Law) of Macau**. The University of Macau will make every effort to protect the personal information held by the University to ensure its confidentiality and integrity.

When the University collects from you, either electronically or in hard copy format, information that can personally identify you, the purposes for the required information will be given. The personal data collected from you may be transferred among different units within the University for processing and use yet will not be disclosed to any third party or organizations outside the University unless otherwise stated, or required by law, or with your prior consent. You can submit a signed request to access or make correction of your personal data held by the University.

### Web site privacy statement

The University of Macau respects the privacy of your personal information by adhering to privacy law. The University of Macau web site privacy statement outlines how the University will manage personal information collected through her web sites. This statement does not extend to external web sites that have been linked from the University web sites. It is suggested that you refer to the privacy statements of these sites.

The University of Macau reserves the right to update the University privacy policy and web site privacy statement at anytime to reflect our web sites and privacy compliance development. Please check these policies periodically for changes.

### Collecting, Using and Disclosing Personal Information

  * **Information Collected**

The University web sites may collect personal information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), and/or educational interests. Such personal information may be requested by us in respect of research, teaching, public service, and/or for administrative purposes.

Web servers typically collect, at least temporarily, the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer being used; the web pages requested; the date and the time of your visit to the site; the type of browser that is being used. The University may collect statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which our web sites are accessed as well as the usage of our web sites.

  * **Use and Disclosure of Collected Information**

If you provide personal details during your visit to the University web sites, then we will only use and disclose your personal information for the purpose for which it was collected. Any other type of use and disclosure will require your prior and definite consent, or be in accordance with privacy law.

  * **Security**

The University of Macau web sites use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the transmission of sensitive personal information over the Internet. Usernames and passwords may be required before personal information (such as exam results) is published on the web site. This is to ensure that information is displayed only to the intended person. 

Although every effort is made to secure network communications, the University cannot ensure the privacy of online communications. Individuals using online services should also take steps to protect personal information, such as closing the web browser when finished using the site, ensuring your password is kept securely and not disclosed to anyone else. If you have concern about conveying your personal information over the Internet, then you may wish to contact the University by telephone or mail.

If you have any questions, please e-mail us at webmaster.

|  |
